{
    "subject": "resource/WKMG-TV",
    "predicate": "property/location",
    "object": "resource/Orlando,_Florida",
    "human_readable": "WKMG-TV is located in Orlando, Florida.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9014796614646912,
            "question": "Where is WKMG-TV located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7404338717460632,
            "question": "What state is WKMG-TV in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6731587052345276,
            "question": "What city is home to WKMG-TV?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6248535513877869,
            "question": "Is WKMG-TV a television station?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4714824855327606,
            "question": "Does WKMG-TV cover local news and events?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.40741971135139465,
            "question": "What type of media does WKMG-TV produce?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3777013421058655,
            "question": "Are there any other well-known television stations in Florida?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.29128754138946533,
            "question": "Can you name a famous landmark in Orlando, Florida?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2301577925682068,
            "question": "What are some popular tourist attractions in Orlando?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.22310179471969604,
            "question": "What is the population of Orlando, Florida?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=WKMG-TV is located in Orlando, Florida.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5998_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some popular tourist attractions in Orlando?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5998_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you name a famous landmark in Orlando, Florida?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5998_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any other well-known television stations in Florida?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5998_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5998_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5998_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5998_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5998_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5998_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5998_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5998_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5998_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5998_9.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5998_92.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After evaluating the context information, I can confirm that:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThis answer is derived from the context information provided, which consistently mentions that WKMG-TV is licensed to and has its studios located in Orlando, Florida."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {'output': 'yes'}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}